Fernando Bohorquez

WEB DEVELOPER

Contact

Address

1770 Broadway St. Ann Arbor 48105

Email

fernnado@cntrl.app

Phone

954-683-2824

Education

Bachelor of Science in Engineering

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor 2015 - 2020

Major: Computer Science

Relevant Coursework: ENTR Marketing, Intro to Machine Learning, Database Mgt. Systems, Web Systems, Intro to OS

Profile

I am a social impact entrepreneur with a computer science background. Technically I focus on web development and machine learning. Business wise I have experience in early stage pre-funding startups. I have experience with UX / UI design. I just recently graduated from the University of Michigan in April 2020.

Experience

Software Engineer

MoxyTech / 2020 - 2020

Start-up focused on supporting the chronic pain community by quantifying pain, directly improving clinician outcomes and facilitating pain research

- Designed and developed a dashboard built around the serverless ecosystem, meant to both cut costs for the company and gain new clients by providing more services
- Built machine learning solutions meant to harness internal data and create new revenue streams

Founder / Web Developer

CNTRL / 2019 - Current

Start-up focused on supporting computer science freelancers in their customer discovery process and early career development.

- Built and led a 5 person team through the customer discovery process (talking to 100+ potential customers), created a go to market strategy, and a viable early prototype
- Participated in the TechTown detroit accelerator, meant to guide small precustomer validation startups to success

Front-End Web Developer

Roseland Day Care Center / 2019 - 2020

Nonprofit, based out of Roseland Chicago, which offers Child Care to high school, college and low income working moms in a nurturing environment.

- With the help of key stakeholders, I researched, designed, iterated, and finally developed, a website meant to increase donations and facilitate community engagement
- Delivered an easy to maintain modern Wordpress website.

Skills

- Adobe XD
- HTML / CSS / JS
- React / Node / Express
- Python
- Pytorch / Flask
- Fluent Spanish

- C++
- MySQL / MongoDB
- Tableau
- Customer Discovery
- Design Thinking
- Conversational French

Certifications

AWS Cloud Practitioner 2020

Google Marketing 2020